That Ajay Singh Rahul Mehta's hello, the
world is traveling because of the virus,
all the scientists are
engaged in the search for vaccination for this epidemic, no
medicine has been
given yet, but there is a good news, Reliance
General Insurance Company has launched an insurance
policy for VAT,
before this policy we understand the point,
as you all know, it is also an
epidemic and it spreads through contact with people
and there is no cure for it yet, there is no
vaccination, till now there is a problem
in lakhs of rupees, it is
not known whether it can spread further or not, then
Lucknow will open, it will open, but no
one knows when this corona will
open, I will make
good use of it, people will go into business, they will come
in contact with people
and what will be the effect of this epidemic, it is
not known, it may
spread again and people may start getting infected, so this is the
first policy of India
which Reliance General Insurance has launched,
its name is Corona Cover Policy from
Reliance General Insurance Company Ltd,
this policy has been launched
in Team Event, Silver, Gold and Flight
A Silver, meaning only  And you
get the benefit of Intel, in Gold there
is mention of positive report of Quarantine Plus and in
Platinum it means that
for those who have travelled internationally, apart from both there is
news of low function
that this policy is well cleaned, 50,000, 1 lakh
and both have policies, only the premium of 2 lakh policy
is 3540 and
its waiting is clear,
this policy will be for a term of 15 days, there is
no need for any test for this
and you can get the policy by making online policy payment, there is a
chakli given in it, by clicking on
your name, if you
do it online then you will get the policy copy in your mail box,
it is absolutely fine
if you have adopted China, then
if you have to go to the point then you will get the
benefit at that time
and if you take the Gold plan then
Quarantine Plus Positive is only Dimple,
you have taken a policy of 2 lakh and have paid
₹500 for 350 things
that if you are found positive at any time in the month then
two-year composition will be given
if you have a mediclaim  So
if someone from the hospital is genuine then you
can also take out a mediclaim policy,
apart from that, complete compensation of Rs 2 lakh or more will be given to the beneficiary
and if there is a
secondary contact that you had
contacted someone and he was found positive then also
you will have to go to the hospital,
in such a situation, now if you go to the hospital in the quantity of illegal point government then
50% two
spoons of butter 1 lakh rupees should be given to you in compensation, right now
this is the right time to
take this policy and this policy can be
taken only for Rs 260, this is an
online policy and there is a policy of 12 months and
now is the right time to take this policy
because if you take it today, if you are
at home in quantity, then the chances of getting an infection are
very less, so
as soon as the quarantine period of these 15 days is over,
this policy will become active and after 15 days,
if we have to go anywhere
or get infected then we will
get the benefits. For more information
You can call me and you
can get it for yourself, for your family
and for all your employees who are working with you,
you can get a small policy for them, like this you
can also get a sudden policy of Rs 25,000 for Rs 25 lakh, the
premium is very low and
this policy is very good for safety measures and this
is Diya and the company that has launched this policy,
for more information you
can call anytime, my phone number is 1234
15051 521, thank you, Lal Mehta,
I am in Bangalore.